# KAVAN PANSURIYA

NETWORK SECURITY ANALYST



## CONTACT



patelkavan210@gmail.com



www https://voldemort.co.in https://website.voldemort.co.in

## PROFILE

Trusted Network Security Engineer with over 1.5+ years protecting companies against attackers who disrupt Web-Applications or Web-Servers. Served as Adviser for showing vulnerabilities, on their websites, to the IT companies. Educates colleagues on best practices and network safety protocols. Protects networked assets through both preventive and reactionary measures,

## EDUCATION

#### **Diploma Of Computer** Engineering

The Maharaja Sayajirao University of Baroda, Baroda 2018-2022

- Last Year Of Diploma In Computer Engineering,
- Pursuing 4+ Courses On Udemy Based On Ethical hacking.
- Preparing for OSCP in 2022.

#### **High School Education**

Shree P.V. Modi School , Rajkot 2007-2018

- From 1st till 10th Thoroughly English Medium Student.
- In 10th Achieved 97.80 Percentile And 80.62 Peroenlage.

## SKILLS

- Critical Thinking
- Financial Resources Management
- Enthusiastic Fresher
- Network Architecture Understanding
- Network Security Management

- Passionate Learner
- Pentesting And Bug Bounty
- Collaborative Ability
- Communication And Interpersonal Skills
- Responsive Web Design

## EXPERIENCE

#### **PORTFOLIO**

#### Feb. 2021 To Present Day

- . Provided front-end website development using HTML, PHP, CSS, etc.
- Deployed and Managed it using Amazon Servers.
- Secured and Fortified it with SSL certificates and Firewall.
- Can check my work at voldemort.co.in.

### OWNER AND NETWORK SECURITY ANALYSTIC RAJKOT, INDIA

#### Feb. 2021 To Present Day

- . Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.
- Collaborated with developers and lead my own team for the project.
- lt's an upcoming project as me and my team is undergoing through its work. Can check it out on website.voldemort.co.in